Carlo Alejandro Bonilla Morales

Software Engineer

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/carlobonilla/ GitHub: https://github.com/cabonillamo Portfolio: https://cabonillamo.github.io/portfolio/ I am a young student in Software Engineering with one year of work experience. I have a strong passion for technology, and I am constantly seeking new opportunities to learn and develop my skills. Specifically, I am passionate about all things related to .NET and enjoy exploring its many applications in software development

Personal Information

Email: carlobonilla640@gmail.com Address: Alajuela, Costa Rica Phone number: (+506) 8501 1597

Education

2021-2024. Bachelor's Degree in Software Engineering (Universidad Técnica Nacional) Accredited by SINAES

2021-2023. Software Engineering Diploma (Universidad Técnica Nacional). Accredited by SINAES

Work Experience

2023-2024. NOC Documenter

Evertec

Within this position I execute the documentation of a program, analyze the source code and document. Additionally, I am responsible for maintaining and updating technical documentation and operational procedures in the Network Operations Center. I am also participating in two projects of which we are clients, and I am carrying out the corresponding quality filters to be able to receive the product in a better way and transfer it to production.

2024 - 2024. IT Analyst

JUPEMA (Junta de Pensiones y Jubilaciones del Magisterio Nacional). Intern

Within this position I execute the documentation of Scrum methodologies on system requirements, speaking with clients and analyzing the maintenance to be done on the systems. I will do this work as an intern to obtain the University degree in August.

Languages

English Intermediate Spanish (native)

References

Provided upon request

Skills

Technical Skills

- C# .NET Framework for WinForms development
- ASP .NET using entity Framework & ADO .NET
- Java (JSF 2.3 & JavaFx)
- jQuery
- Scrum Methodology
- Angular
- Node js
- ISS
- Office
- Typescript
- JavaScript
- Git
- C++
- SQL Server And Oracle
- Azure
- Linux

Desing Patterns-architectures

Knowledge in MVC, facade pattern, Singleton pattern, factory pattern, N- layers, Clean Architecture

<u>Database</u>

SQL Server and Oracle (DML & DDL, Stored procedures, SQL query's)

Projects

Condominium Management:

Developed in C# asp .net framework using MVC & entity framework. https://github.com/Anibal-Alpizar/aspnet-condominium-management

Payroll Management:

Developed in java JSF 2.3. https://github.com/Anibal-Alpizar/jsp-sql-planillas

Website for a Mechanical workshop

Developed in HTML, CSS, SQL Bootstrap5& JavaScript. https://github.com/cabonillamo/proyectotaller

Marketplace Project-Buy and sell management

Developed in node.js, Angular, HTML, CSS, MySql & TypeScript.

https://github.com/anibalalpizar/angular-marketplaceexpress